 [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which CSS property allows you to hide an element but still maintain the space it occupies on the web page",
        "answers" : [
            "display:none;","visibility:hidden", "display:hidden", "none:hidden"
        ],
         "correct" : "visibility:hidden"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid CSS length unit?",
        "answers" : [
            "cm","em", "dm", "All of the above"
        ],
         "correct" : "dm"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is the CSS selector which allows you to target every element in a web page?",
        "answers" : [
            "*",":: root", ">", "<"
        ],
         "correct" : "*"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which of the following CSS properties DOES NOT influence the box model?",
        "answers" : [
            "Outline","Padding", "Contnent"
        ],
         "correct" : "Outline"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "How will you select the anchor element whose href attribute starts with https?",
        "answers" : [
            "a[href*='https","a[href^='https", "a[href$='https", "a[href~='https"
        ],
         "correct" : "a[href^='https"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What CSS3 property is used for capitalizing the text or converting them to lowercase or uppercase?",
        "answers" : [
            "text-transform","text-translate", "text-convert", "text-format"
        ],
         "correct" : "a[href^='https"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What property should be used in case we need to display a nice blue border that is dotted in nature around an image?",
        "answers" : [
            "border-dotted","border-line", "border-style", "border-decoration"
        ],
         "correct" : "border-dotted"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which among the following options represent correct syntax for selecting all paragraph elements in a div element?",
        "answers" : [
            "div + p","div < p", "div p", "div - p"
        ],
         "correct" : "div p"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What CSS3 property is used for the set distance between borders of adjacent tables cells?",
        "answers" : [
            "border-spacing","border-collapse", "cell-spacing", "cell-colapse"
        ],
         "correct" : "border-spacing"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which of the below options are used for defining the difference between two lines of the content?",
        "answers" : [
            "line-distance","line-gap", "line-height", "line-min"
        ],
         "correct" : "line-height"
    }


]
